const questions = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Language is often said to be an intrinsic inheritance of man because:",
        "options": [
            "Man is homo sapiens",
            "It is only man that uses language as a verbal medium of expression",
            "Language is a medium of communication",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "It is only man that uses language as a verbal medium of expression"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "The study which focuses on the variations of language use in the common Society is ______",
        "options": [
            "Anthropology",
            "Sociology",
            "Onomastics",
            "Sociolinguistic"
        ],
        "answer": "Sociolinguistic"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which of the following is not true about man and the use of language",
        "options": [
            "Man is a monolingual creature",
            "Man can be a bilingual person",
            "A child born without any vocal or auditory impairment can acquire the language of his environment",
            "Every man has a mother tongue"
        ],
        "answer": "Man is a monolingual creature"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a definition of language?",
        "options": [
            "A vehicle that helps man to convey his feelings, thoughts or ideas",
            "A verbal means of communication",
            "A means of communication",
            "A culture artifact"
        ],
        "answer": "A culture artifact"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Sign language is to ______ what verbal language is to ______?",
        "options": [
            "Bees and crocodile",
            "Computer and radio",
            "The deaf/the dumb and normal human beings",
            "The honey bee, dogs and communication network"
        ],
        "answer": "The deaf/the dumb and normal human beings"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which of the following is not one of the approaches for the definition of language?",
        "options": [
            "The structure-based approach",
            "The culture-based approach",
            "The interactive approach",
            "The semiotic approach"
        ],
        "answer": "The semiotic approach"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which of the following is not one of the theories which account for the origin of language?",
        "options": [
            "The bow-wow theory",
            "The hindu-religious theory",
            "The Christian religious theory",
            "The symbolic theory"
        ],
        "answer": "The symbolic theory"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "______ according to the biblical account was the first man to use language",
        "options": [
            "Abraham",
            "Moses",
            "Adam",
            "Jacob"
        ],
        "answer": "Adam"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "A community that uses and understand a common language is called",
        "options": [
            "A social community",
            "A speech community",
            "An agnate community",
            "A monolithic community"
        ],
        "answer": "A speech community"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which of the following is not one of the characteristics of language?",
        "options": [
            "language is dynamic",
            "language is productive",
            "language is conventional or arbitrary",
            "language cannot die and its vocabulary is permanent"
        ],
        "answer": "language cannot die and its vocabulary is permanent"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Speech repertoire is a term used to refer to______",
        "options": [
            "The whole language, dialects and their variations which a community or an individual has",
            "The speech nuances of an individual",
            "The linguistic competence of a person",
            "The discourse competence of a speaker"
        ],
        "answer": "The whole language, dialects and their variations which a community or an individual has"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Verbal repertoire could be called all of these below except",
        "options": [
            "Code of repertoire",
            "Linguistic repertoire",
            "Speech repertoire",
            "Linguistic etiquette"
        ],
        "answer": "Linguistic etiquette"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Linguistic nationalism may be used to describe the function of language as",
        "options": [
            "An instrument for conferring social identity on the user",
            "An instrument of propaganda",
            "A dress of thought",
            "An instrument of political debates"
        ],
        "answer": "An instrument for conferring social identity on the user"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "The total number of language in the world is estimated as",
        "options": [
            "6000",
            "7000",
            "450",
            "5000"
        ],
        "answer": "7000"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "A person who can speak and use different language well may be called a______",
        "options": [
            "Bilingual person",
            "Monolingual",
            "Trilingual",
            "Polyglot"
        ],
        "answer": "Polyglot"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is false?",
        "options": [
            "Languages have family",
            "languages is creative",
            "Languages can be used for Phatic communion",
            "Nigerian languages are Mutually unintelligible"
        ],
        "answer": "Nigerian languages are Mutually unintelligible"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "In Nigeria, the ______ and the ______ languages have the status of a second language",
        "options": [
            "English and French",
            "German and English",
            "English and Portuguese",
            "Spanish and French"
        ],
        "answer": "English and French"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "The domains of the English language in Nigeria does not include the use as the language of",
        "options": [
            "Education",
            "Legislation and politics",
            "Mass media and religious",
            "Culture and divination"
        ],
        "answer": "Culture and divination"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "The countries in west Africa where the English language is used as an official language or a second language are",
        "options": [
            "Gabon and Ghana",
            "Sierra Leone and Niger Republic",
            "Cameroon and Nigeria",
            "Nigeria and Ghana"
        ],
        "answer": "Nigeria and Ghana"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Which one of the following is an odd member of the series?",
        "options": [
            "English",
            "Igbo",
            "French",
            "Latin"
        ],
        "answer": "Latin"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "An example of an exoglossic language is",
        "options": [
            "English",
            "Yoruba",
            "Hausa",
            "Efik"
        ],
        "answer": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "A dialect can best be defined as ___",
        "options": [
            "Language variation due to user location and status",
            "Language variation due to politics",
            "Language variation due to users' occupation",
            "Language variation due to policy"
        ],
        "answer": "Language variation due to user location and status"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Nigeria can best described as",
        "options": [
            "A monolingual society",
            "A bilingual society",
            "A multilingual society",
            "A trilingual society"
        ],
        "answer": "A multilingual society"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "___ is best described as a vernacular or an ethic language in Nigeria",
        "options": [
            "Portuguese",
            "Arabic",
            "German",
            "Hausa"
        ],
        "answer": "Hausa"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "The ability of an individual to use two language for communication is",
        "options": [
            "Bilingualism",
            "Monolingualism",
            "Trilingualism",
            "Consumerism"
        ],
        "answer": "Bilingualism"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Which of the following pairs does not describe a type of language discussed in this course?",
        "options": [
            "Mother tongue and second language",
            "Foreign language and national language",
            "National language and official language",
            "Gutter language and diglossia"
        ],
        "answer": "Gutter language and diglossia"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Idiolect is best described as",
        "options": [
            "The characteristics speech of a person",
            "The speech habits of a family",
            "The speech nuances of people in a speech community",
            "The way words are articulated"
        ],
        "answer": "The characteristics speech of a person"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Jargon simply means",
        "options": [
            "The use of meaningless words",
            "The use of a language variety normally used in a specific professional field",
            "The use of bombastic and meaningless expression",
            "The use of creoles"
        ],
        "answer": "The use of a language variety normally used in a specific professional field"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "The term basilect is a term used to describe:",
        "options": [
            "a low language variety",
            "a prestigious language variety",
            "the language of the highly educated people in a society",
            "legalese"
        ],
        "answer": "a low language variety"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "The standard or the prestigious variety of a language used especially in a society with diglossia is often described as:",
        "options": [
            "mesolect",
            "dialect",
            "acrolect",
            "patois"
        ],
        "answer": "acrolect"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "The insertion of a word or a phrase/clause from one language to another in a communication event is known as",
        "options": [
            "code crossing",
            "code switching",
            "code matching",
            "code building"
        ],
        "answer": "code switching"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a form of dialect:",
        "options": [
            "regional dialect",
            "social dialect",
            "historical dialect",
            "archaisms"
        ],
        "answer": "archaisms"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "A diatype is best described as:",
        "options": [
            "language variety according to use",
            "language variety according to user",
            "language variety according to interference",
            "language variety according to education"
        ],
        "answer": "language variety according to use"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "The major determinants of diaypes include all except:",
        "options": [
            "field or subject matter",
            "tenor or the social relationships between the participants in the context of language use",
            "mode, formality or the informality of the context",
            "the cohesive elements in the communication event"
        ],
        "answer": "the cohesive elements in the communication event"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "The four major language skills does not include:",
        "options": [
            "listening and speaking",
            "punctuation",
            "reading",
            "writing"
        ],
        "answer": "punctuation"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "The English language can best be described as a_ in Nigeria",
        "options": [
            "a colonial legacy now used as lingua franca",
            "the policy of Sir Fredrick Lord Lugard",
            "the result of Macpherson constitution",
            "the UNESCO policy on language transfer"
        ],
        "answer": "a colonial legacy now used as lingua franca"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Br E is a symbol used to represent:",
        "options": [
            "a regional variety of English known as British English",
            "a linguistic organization known as British reading experts",
            "an association of British radio engineers",
            "a variety of English known as black regional English"
        ],
        "answer": "a regional variety of English known as British English"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "The English language is often described by linguists as:",
        "options": [
            "a syllable-timed language",
            "a stress-timed language",
            "a classical language",
            "a mono-syllabic language"
        ],
        "answer": "a stress-timed language"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "The term world Englishes is",
        "options": [
            "an abstraction",
            "a misnomer",
            "a term used to describe the diaspora varieties of English across the globe",
            "a word that accounts for English for specific purposes"
        ],
        "answer": "a term used to describe the diaspora varieties of English across the globe"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "The use of the English language as a vehicle of national communication dates back to the establishment of the colony of Lagos by the British colonial masters in",
        "options": [
            "1862",
            "1960",
            "1772",
            "1528"
        ],
        "answer": "1862"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "A world language is ___ and an example of such a language is ___",
        "options": [
            "a language used extensively across the globe, the English language",
            "a language studied as a foreign language in African countries, Portuguese",
            "a language used as the language of the mass media, German",
            "a language used extensively for religion and commerce, the French language"
        ],
        "answer": "a language used extensively across the globe, the English language"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "A language which has no native speakers and is nobody's language but is rather a contact language is",
        "options": [
            "jargon",
            "legalese",
            "pidgin English",
            "pidgin"
        ],
        "answer": "pidgin"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "A group language is",
        "options": [
            "the language used for communication by an ethnic group or a cultural group",
            "the language used in the capital territory of a nation",
            "the language used in teaching and learning",
            "an inter-ethnic language"
        ],
        "answer": "the language used for communication by an ethnic group or a cultural group"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "The following words refer to the same type of language except",
        "options": [
            "contact language",
            "trade language",
            "link language",
            "technical language"
        ],
        "answer": "technical language"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Which of the following is not true of dialects:",
        "options": [
            "they share the same grammatical structure with their standard languages",
            "they differ in aspects of phonology",
            "they differ in some aspects of vocabulary",
            "they have a common lexicon"
        ],
        "answer": "they have a common lexicon"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "In Nigeria, pidgin is used in some of the multilingual communities as a type of",
        "options": [
            "romance language",
            "lingua franca",
            "phatic communion",
            "poetic language"
        ],
        "answer": "lingua franca"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "With the following may not be categorized as a city of the English language?",
        "options": [
            "user-related variety",
            "use-related variety",
            "formal variety",
            "nominalization"
        ],
        "answer": "nominalization"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "The standard variety of English can best be defined as",
        "options": [
            "the dialect of English accorded a high level of prestige and accepted as standard by planning and policy initiatives of the government",
            "the social dialect of the language",
            "the historical dialect of English",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "the dialect of English accorded a high level of prestige and accepted as standard by planning and policy initiatives of the government"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "Which of the following may not be associated with standard English?",
        "options": [
            "It is an intersection of dialect and function variation",
            "it developed from the London dialect of English",
            "it has standard grammar and universal vocabulary",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "none of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "Which of the following may not be considered in the discussion of English language variety by usage:",
        "options": [
            "field of discourse",
            "medium",
            "discourse style",
            "creolization"
        ],
        "answer": "creolization"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "Field of discourse simply means:",
        "options": [
            "mode",
            "tenor",
            "corpus",
            "subject-matter"
        ],
        "answer": "subject-matter"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "Which of the following may not be associated with the English language as an international language?",
        "options": [
            "Over 914 million people speak the English language across the nations of the world",
            "More than 326 million people use the English language as a first language",
            "About 312,626,449 people use it either as a second or a foreign language",
            "The English language did not originate from a dialect of West Germanic language"
        ],
        "answer": "The English language did not originate from a dialect of West Germanic language"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "The machinery utilized for the expression of our thoughts and feeling is",
        "options": [
            "Grammar",
            "Language",
            "Syntax",
            "Communication"
        ],
        "answer": "Language"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "The fact that there is no formal relationship between words and who they represent implies that language is",
        "options": [
            "performative",
            "discrete",
            "arbitrary",
            "generative"
        ],
        "answer": "arbitrary"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "'Hook' and 'Look' exemplify that language is",
        "options": [
            "discrete",
            "a human property",
            "dynamic",
            "indispensable"
        ],
        "answer": "discrete"
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "The language which a person acquires from his first contact with his environment is called",
        "options": [
            "foreign language",
            "social language",
            "mother tongue",
            "second language"
        ],
        "answer": "mother tongue"
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "The mother tongue may also be referred to as",
        "options": [
            "inter language",
            "intralanguage",
            "primary language",
            "first language"
        ],
        "answer": "first language"
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "The English language is studied in Nigeria as",
        "options": [
            "first language",
            "lingua franca",
            "second language",
            "official language"
        ],
        "answer": "second language"
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "The language which enjoys constitutional backing to be used in Nigeria for official purposes is",
        "options": [
            "national language",
            "lingua franca",
            "mother tongue",
            "first language"
        ],
        "answer": "national language"
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "______ is used in a multilingual society like Nigeria to facilitate communication",
        "options": [
            "pidgin English",
            "lingua franca",
            "official language",
            "national language"
        ],
        "answer": "lingua franca"
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "Which of the following is not true?",
        "options": [
            "Nigeria is a multilingual society",
            "Nigeria is a monolingual society",
            "Language is the sole property of man",
            "English is the official language in Nigeria"
        ],
        "answer": "Nigeria is a monolingual society"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "Two among the hindrances to effective use of English in Nigeria are ______ and ______",
        "options": [
            "Lack of qualified teachers and unconducive environment",
            "Synonyms and antonyms",
            "Conscious and unconscious efforts",
            "Intrinsic and extrinsic factors"
        ],
        "answer": "Lack of qualified teachers and unconducive environment"
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "The varieties of English according to region are known as",
        "options": [
            "dialects",
            "idiolects",
            "mesolects",
            "pidgin"
        ],
        "answer": "dialects"
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "The two main varieties of English language according to region are ______ and ______",
        "options": [
            "Yoruba and Igbo",
            "British and American",
            "official and national languages",
            "standard and sub-standard English"
        ],
        "answer": "British and American"
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "The study of dialects is described as",
        "options": [
            "grammar",
            "syntax",
            "dialectology",
            "register"
        ],
        "answer": "dialectology"
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "Two of the linguistic features with differentiate one dialect of the English from others are ______ and ______",
        "options": [
            "pronunciation and spelling",
            "intonation and stress",
            "singular and plural",
            "words and opposites"
        ],
        "answer": "pronunciation and spelling"
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "The result of a blend of indigenous languages with foreign languages in African societies is called",
        "options": [
            "pidgin",
            "interference",
            "lingua franca",
            "language growth"
        ],
        "answer": "pidgin"
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "When a Nigerian learner of the English language does not exhibit deep need to master the language, his kind of problem is called",
        "options": [
            "societal bilingualism",
            "learner-induced",
            "teacher induced",
            "environmental"
        ],
        "answer": "learner-induced"
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "The Igbo speakers and users of the English language have the problem of pronouncing the consonant",
        "options": [
            "/r/",
            "/v/",
            "/b/",
            "/g/"
        ],
        "answer": "/r/"
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "One of the negative impacts of English in Nigeria is",
        "options": [
            "erosion of cultural values",
            "unification of the country",
            "it solves communication problem",
            "it builds national identity"
        ],
        "answer": "erosion of cultural values"
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "Linguistics is concerned with the",
        "options": [
            "formation of words",
            "harmonization of words",
            "scientific study of language",
            "language assessment"
        ],
        "answer": "scientific study of language"
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "The term which is used to refer to the topic being discussed is called",
        "options": [
            "tenor",
            "mode",
            "region",
            "field"
        ],
        "answer": "field"
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "The English verb is often stressed on the ______ syllable in American English",
        "options": [
            "first",
            "second",
            "third",
            "fourth"
        ],
        "answer": "first"
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "The English language in Nigeria can be best described as",
        "options": [
            "second language",
            "first language",
            "lingua franca",
            "mother tongue"
        ],
        "answer": "lingua franca"
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "______ during speech is capable of information distortion",
        "options": [
            "mother tongue interference",
            "second language acquisition",
            "interpretation",
            "low social class"
        ],
        "answer": "mother tongue interference"
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "Apart from Nigeria, two other African countries where English is official language are and",
        "options": [
            "Ghana and Cameroon",
            "Chad and Niger",
            "Ghana and Sierra Leone",
            "Zambia and Egypt"
        ],
        "answer": "Ghana and Sierra Leone"
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "The two major varieties of English language are ______ and ______",
        "options": [
            "Nigeria and south Africa",
            "British and Australia",
            "American and New-Zealand",
            "British and American"
        ],
        "answer": "British and American"
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "Br E stands for",
        "options": [
            "Beginner English",
            "Borrowed English",
            "Broken English",
            "British English"
        ],
        "answer": "British English"
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "The American English is represented by the symbol",
        "options": [
            "AmE",
            "Ar E",
            "ALE",
            "AEE"
        ],
        "answer": "AmE"
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "The full meaning of ESP is",
        "options": [
            "English for special purposes",
            "English for social purposes",
            "English for specific purposes",
            "English for semantic purposes"
        ],
        "answer": "English for specific purposes"
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is not true?",
        "options": [
            "A child learns a language",
            "A child acquires a language",
            "A child does not make any conscious effort in language acquisition",
            "Language learning involves conscious effort"
        ],
        "answer": "A child learns a language"
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "The use of two languages in a speech community is described as",
        "options": [
            "multilingualism",
            "bilingualism",
            "monolingualism",
            "double tongue"
        ],
        "answer": "bilingualism"
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "A person who speaks Igbo, Hausa and English languages is called",
        "options": [
            "multilingual",
            "bilingual",
            "monolingual",
            "language transfer"
        ],
        "answer": "multilingual"
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "Bilingualism and multilingualism are ______ terms associated with the combined use of languages",
        "options": [
            "sociolinguistics",
            "interference",
            "academics",
            "bilingual"
        ],
        "answer": "sociolinguistics"
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "L1 means",
        "options": [
            "first language",
            "language of education",
            "language study",
            "second language"
        ],
        "answer": "first language"
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "L2 stands for",
        "options": [
            "English as a second language",
            "second language",
            "British English",
            "native language"
        ],
        "answer": "second language"
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "When a speaker transfers the features and structures of his first language to the target language, the situation is described as:",
        "options": [
            "language transfer",
            "language contact",
            "mother tongue interference",
            "mother tongue transfer"
        ],
        "answer": "mother tongue interference"
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "When the speech patterns of a first language hinders the effective pronunciation of the second language, ______ is said to have occurred",
        "options": [
            "phonological interference",
            "morphological interference",
            "semantic interference",
            "adult language transfer"
        ],
        "answer": "phonological interference"
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "If a second language user refers to 'cooker' as one who cooks, this exemplifies",
        "options": [
            "grammatical interference",
            "semantic interference",
            "morphological interference",
            "phonological interference"
        ],
        "answer": "morphological interference"
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": "\"Cutted\" and \"hitted\" are examples of_ interference",
        "options": [
            "phonological",
            "morphological",
            "grammatical",
            "semantic"
        ],
        "answer": "morphological"
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "The expression \"The teacher is not on seat\" shows",
        "options": [
            "grammatical interference",
            "level of education",
            "morphological interference",
            "second language factor"
        ],
        "answer": "grammatical interference"
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "Arbitrariness as a feature of language means that",
        "options": [
            "language is constant",
            "language is dynamic",
            "there is no formal relationship between words and what they represent",
            "words are not the same"
        ],
        "answer": "there is no formal relationship between words and what they represent"
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": "___is the property of man which sets him apart from other animals",
        "options": [
            "speech",
            "signs",
            "meaning",
            "listening"
        ],
        "answer": "speech"
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true?",
        "options": [
            "Standard English refers to the variety of English acceptable to the English audience worldwide",
            "Standard English is the English language spoken in Britain only",
            "The American English is not standard English",
            "Standard English is not the international English"
        ],
        "answer": "Standard English refers to the variety of English acceptable to the English audience worldwide"
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "The fact that there are some differences in the way people speak a language explains",
        "options": [
            "varieties according to user",
            "varieties according to use",
            "language difference",
            "British variety"
        ],
        "answer": "varieties according to user"
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "\"Vest\" and \"Undershirt\" represent",
        "options": [
            "differences in lexis",
            "differences in orthography",
            "differences in stress",
            "differences in syntax"
        ],
        "answer": "differences in lexis"
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "_ is used to explain what people do with language in various human activities",
        "options": [
            "word",
            "register",
            "dialects",
            "idiolect"
        ],
        "answer": "register"
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "The belief that a speaker has a repertoire of varieties and habitually switches to the appropriate one as occasion arises is called",
        "options": [
            "Varieties according to subject matter",
            "Varieties according to style of discourse",
            "Varieties according to medium of discourse",
            "Varieties according to purpose"
        ],
        "answer": "Varieties according to subject matter"
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "The relationship between language and the purpose for which particular piece of writing is designed is described as",
        "options": [
            "medium",
            "style",
            "attitude",
            "manner"
        ],
        "answer": "style"
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "Which of the following is not true?",
        "options": [
            "In a formal language, the writer establishes impersonal relationship with his audience",
            "The third person pronoun is preferred to the first and second person in formal language",
            "Digressions are features of an informal language",
            "Language associated with a particular region or social group is accepted in a formal communication"
        ],
        "answer": "Language associated with a particular region or social group is accepted in a formal communication"
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "___ is defined as a set of codes of arbitrary vocal symbols and signs for communication in a speech community",
        "options": [
            "words",
            "gestures",
            "language",
            "lingua franca"
        ],
        "answer": "language"
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "Technolect is",
        "options": [
            "the language associated with lawyers",
            "the language of builders",
            "the language of technology",
            "the language of chemistry"
        ],
        "answer": "the language of technology"
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "A good dictionary is described as a",
        "options": [
            "good companion",
            "biography of words",
            "orthography of words",
            "good mentor"
        ],
        "answer": "biography of words"
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "Another name for the abridged dictionary is",
        "options": [
            "Longman dictionary",
            "desk dictionary",
            "oxford dictionary",
            "foreign dictionary"
        ],
        "answer": "desk dictionary"
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "Which of the following is a time prefix?",
        "options": [
            "post-",
            "pre-",
            "ex-",
            "fore-"
        ],
        "answer": "post-"
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "Which of the following prefixes indicates one?",
        "options": [
            "multi-",
            "bi-",
            "tri-",
            "uni-"
        ],
        "answer": "uni-"
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "The word \"playboy\" illustrates",
        "options": [
            "clipping",
            "compounds",
            "blending",
            "conversion"
        ],
        "answer": "compounds"
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "___is a functional shift in a word which has not undergone an inflection",
        "options": [
            "conversion",
            "lending",
            "back formation",
            "clipping"
        ],
        "answer": "conversion"
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "The combination of two separate forms of words to get a new word is called",
        "options": [
            "clipping",
            "borrowing",
            "blending",
            "compounds"
        ],
        "answer": "blending"
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "While NECO represents____, U.N.N represents____",
        "options": [
            "acronym/antonym",
            "synonym/abbreviation",
            "abbreviation/acronym",
            "acronym/abbreviation"
        ],
        "answer": "abbreviation/acronym"
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "Words that are recognized by a person but he does not make use of them are called",
        "options": [
            "passive vocabulary",
            "active vocabulary",
            "pseudo vocabulary",
            "words"
        ],
        "answer": "passive vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "A syntagmatic relationship which exists between words and determines their co-occurrence is",
        "options": [
            "ation",
            "syntagm",
            "synonym",
            "homophones"
        ],
        "answer": "ation"
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "___is the addition of prefix and suffix to a root word",
        "options": [
            "prefixation",
            "affixation",
            "clipping",
            "suffixation"
        ],
        "answer": "affixation"
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "Words such as \"Dorabuchi\" and \"Arabellion\" are examples of",
        "options": [
            "conventions",
            "coinages",
            "adaptations",
            "fragments"
        ],
        "answer": "coinages"
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "___is described as the actual words we make use of in speech and writing",
        "options": [
            "active vocabulary",
            "formal speech",
            "register",
            "passive vocabulary"
        ],
        "answer": "active vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "The words \"twixt\" and \"thou\" are examples of words",
        "options": [
            "informal",
            "colloquial",
            "archaic",
            "formal"
        ],
        "answer": "archaic"
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "The word \"mouse\" as an animal and 'mouse' as a device connected to a computer are examples of____",
        "options": [
            "homonyms",
            "homophones",
            "antonyms",
            "synonyms"
        ],
        "answer": "homonyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "The two popular types of dictionaries are ___ and ___",
        "options": [
            "Longman and oxford",
            "abridged and unabridged",
            "English and French",
            "contemporary and ancient"
        ],
        "answer": "abridged and unabridged"
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "The dictionary meaning of words is described as the ___ level of meaning",
        "options": [
            "denotative",
            "connotative",
            "synthesis",
            "literary"
        ],
        "answer": "denotative"
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "In the word \"carefulness\", ful and 'ness' are called",
        "options": [
            "prefixes",
            "suffixes",
            "prefix and suffix",
            "opposi"
        ],
        "answer": "suffixes"
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "The word 'editorials' belongs to register",
        "options": [
            "sports",
            "law",
            "religion",
            "journalism"
        ],
        "answer": "journalism"
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "\"Pail\" and 'pale' are examples of ___",
        "options": [
            "homophones",
            "homonyms",
            "synonyms",
            "polysemy"
        ],
        "answer": "homophones"
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "Words in the dictionary are arranged in__",
        "options": [
            "volumetric order",
            "numerical order",
            "classical order",
            "alphabetical order"
        ],
        "answer": "alphabetical order"
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "Which of the following words is correctly spelt?",
        "options": [
            "Pronounciation",
            "auxilliary",
            "neccessary",
            "accommodation"
        ],
        "answer": "accommodation"
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "Words that are nearly the same in meaning are said to be",
        "options": [
            "antonymou",
            "polysemous",
            "synonymous",
            "homophonous"
        ],
        "answer": "synonymous"
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "A word which is capable of eliciting two or more different meanings and the meaning share the same semantic field is said to be",
        "options": [
            "polysemous",
            "acronym",
            "synonymous",
            "homophonous"
        ],
        "answer": "polysemous"
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "The words \"spinster\" and \"bachelor\" are ______",
        "options": [
            "antonymous",
            "synonymous",
            "similar",
            "the same"
        ],
        "answer": "antonymous"
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "Quirk and Greenaburn classify register according to ______ and ______",
        "options": [
            "meaning, purpose and function",
            "type, class and style",
            "field of discourse, medium of discourse and style of discourse",
            "stress, intonation and manner"
        ],
        "answer": "field of discourse, medium of discourse and style of discourse"
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "The Longman Dictionary of Contemporary English is an example of dictionary",
        "options": [
            "English",
            "French",
            "abridged",
            "unabridged"
        ],
        "answer": "unabridged"
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "Words that are spelt and pronounced alike but have different origin and meaning are called",
        "options": [
            "homonyms",
            "homophones",
            "acronyms",
            "antonyms"
        ],
        "answer": "homonyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "The words \"mail\" and \"mail\" exemplify ______",
        "options": [
            "acronyms",
            "homonyms",
            "homophones",
            "antonyms"
        ],
        "answer": "homonyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "A word that is formed from the first letters of words that form an expression is referred to as",
        "options": [
            "abbreviations",
            "abridgement",
            "acronyms",
            "mnemonics"
        ],
        "answer": "acronyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "The major difference between polysemous words and homonyms is",
        "options": [
            "Polysemous words have the same meaning",
            "Homonyms share the same meaning",
            "Polysemous word share the same semantic field",
            "Homonyms share the same semantic field"
        ],
        "answer": "Polysemous word share the same semantic field"
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "The vocabulary of English refers to:",
        "options": [
            "structure in the language",
            "the total stock of words in the language",
            "the lexemes",
            "the phonemic structure of the language"
        ],
        "answer": "the total stock of words in the language"
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "Active vocabulary is a term which is used to describe:",
        "options": [
            "active words in the language",
            "words which have a huge array of new synonyms",
            "words whose antonyms are converse in nature",
            "the familiar and known words in the language which a person can correctly and effectively use"
        ],
        "answer": "the familiar and known words in the language which a person can correctly and effectively use"
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "Receptive vocabulary are:",
        "options": [
            "words in the English language which a person can fairly understand when he encounters them in a text but may not be able to use them correctly",
            "words in the mental map of a person which he has good mastery of",
            "words which are mainly in the colloquial domain",
            "words which are predominantly in the formal domain used for serious discourse"
        ],
        "answer": "words in the English language which a person can fairly understand when he encounters them in a text but may not be able to use them correctly"
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "Officialese are to office administration what is to the law discipline:",
        "options": [
            "luminary",
            "clients",
            "legalese",
            "judiciary"
        ],
        "answer": "legalese"
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "Monosemous words are",
        "options": [
            "mono-syllabic words",
            "words with a single meaning",
            "words which are static in nature",
            "non-gradable words"
        ],
        "answer": "words with a single meaning"
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "Which of the following may not be regarded as a method of vocabulary development for a second language learner:",
        "options": [
            "extensive reading",
            "the use of morphological processes",
            "The use of word lists and dictionaries",
            "Regression"
        ],
        "answer": "Regression"
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "Passive vocabulary is",
        "options": [
            "words in a dictionary",
            "Words a person can identify or recognize in the reading process but does not make use of",
            "Vulgarians",
            "Archaic words"
        ],
        "answer": "Words a person can identify or recognize in the reading process but does not make use of"
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "Which of the following is not one of the ways through which words could be formed in the English language:",
        "options": [
            "addition of prefixes to a root word",
            "addition of suffixes to a root word",
            "addition of infixes between a prefix and a root word",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "none of the above"
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is false:",
        "options": [
            "prefixation is a morphological process",
            "Prefixation always changes the meaning of the root or the base word to which it is attached",
            "Prefixation usually allies the meaning of the root or the base word",
            "Prefixation is one of the strategies an ESL learner could learn how to develop new words"
        ],
        "answer": "Prefixation always changes the meaning of the root or the base word to which it is attached"
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "The following prefixes are paired with this correct meanings except:",
        "options": [
            "poly-many",
            "bi- two",
            "cente- wrong",
            "re-again or back"
        ],
        "answer": "cente- wrong"
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "Suffixation often produces:",
        "options": [
            "a change in the word order",
            "a change in the medium",
            "a change in the mode",
            "a change in the word class"
        ],
        "answer": "a change in the word class"
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "Suffixes always",
        "options": [
            "come after the base",
            "come before the base",
            "come in the middle of the base",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "come after the base"
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "Affixation in the word building process in the English language includes all except:",
        "options": [
            "prefixation",
            "suffixation",
            "infixation",
            "blends"
        ],
        "answer": "blends"
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is not true of synonymy:",
        "options": [
            "it is mainly a bilateral symmetrical sense relation in which a number of linguistic forms are said to have the same conceptual or propositional meaning",
            "in synonymy meaning is not exact but nearly the same",
            "the words may not always be completely interchangeable",
            "the words are always interchangeable"
        ],
        "answer": "the words are always interchangeable"
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "Wife and husband can be given as an example of:",
        "options": [
            "converse antonym",
            "flexible antonym",
            "gradable antonym",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "converse antonym"
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "Which of the following is a typical characteristic of typonyms:",
        "options": [
            "they represent asymmetrical synonyms",
            "they show discordant relationships",
            "they do not have a superordinate",
            "term to which they belong"
        ],
        "answer": "they represent asymmetrical synonyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "The term meronymy is used to described",
        "options": [
            "a part-whole relationship",
            "a whole-whole relationship",
            "a fractional relationship",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "a part-whole relationship"
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "In the group-tree, root, branch, tree is an example of a",
        "options": [
            "the auxiliary term",
            "the superordinate term",
            "the subordinate term",
            "the near synonym"
        ],
        "answer": "the superordinate term"
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "The term that best describes the words branch and root in their ses relationship with the word tree is",
        "options": [
            "hyperbole",
            "co-meronyms",
            "antonyms",
            "acronyms"
        ],
        "answer": "co-meronyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "Which of the following will not apply to lexical words:",
        "options": [
            "they are also called full words",
            "they are called content words",
            "they are usually unlimited in number",
            "they are grammatical words"
        ],
        "answer": "they are grammatical words"
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "Which of the following is an odd member of the series:",
        "options": [
            "Nouns",
            "Adjectives",
            "Verbs",
            "Pronouns"
        ],
        "answer": "Pronouns"
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "question": "Which of the following terms cannot be used to describe function words:",
        "options": [
            "grammatical words",
            "employ words",
            "empathic words",
            "functors"
        ],
        "answer": "empathic words"
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "Lexical words are prone to diachronic change; This means that:",
        "options": [
            "they change in form or meaning over time",
            "they are inelastic",
            "they are time bad",
            "time has no effect on their form and meaning"
        ],
        "answer": "they change in form or meaning over time"
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "question": "Content words constitute ______ class of words in the English language",
        "options": [
            "a close-ended",
            "an open-ended",
            "a limited",
            "an inelastic"
        ],
        "answer": "an open-ended"
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "question": "The verb forms: come, comes, coming, came, come can be said to be derived from a single_",
        "options": [
            "affix",
            "suffix",
            "infix",
            "lexeme"
        ],
        "answer": "lexeme"
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "question": "Which of the following words is not a functor:",
        "options": [
            "you",
            "could",
            "but",
            "man"
        ],
        "answer": "man"
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "question": "Grammatical words are usually",
        "options": [
            "open-ended in their membership",
            "limited in their membership",
            "perfectly elastic in their membership",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "limited in their membership"
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "question": "Which of the following words does not contain a prefix, an infix and a suffix?",
        "options": [
            "Insubordination",
            "insurmountable",
            "Disestablishmentarianism",
            "inexpensiveness"
        ],
        "answer": "inexpensiveness"
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "Words with the same form but different meanings and have identical pronunciation are best described as:",
        "options": [
            "paronyms",
            "hyponyms",
            "homonyms",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "homonyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "question": "Quay and key are examples of:",
        "options": [
            "empty words",
            "paronyms",
            "homophones",
            "antonyms"
        ],
        "answer": "homophones"
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "question": "The words derived from the same root but which have acquired different meanings are called",
        "options": [
            "synonyms",
            "homophones",
            "litote",
            "paronyms"
        ],
        "answer": "paronyms"
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "question": "The words stationary and stationery are examples of ___",
        "options": [
            "patois",
            "paronyms",
            "homophones",
            "homonyms"
        ],
        "answer": "homophones"
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "question": "The special room or structure built for dogs is called:",
        "options": [
            "cage",
            "pen",
            "house",
            "kennel"
        ],
        "answer": "kennel"
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "question": "The Head of Department has collected his monthly ______ from the cash office for the up-keep of the office",
        "options": [
            "imprest",
            "alimony",
            "dividend",
            "overdraught"
        ],
        "answer": "imprest"
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "question": "The author complained that his publishers have not paid him any ______ since the past ten years:",
        "options": [
            "fund",
            "allowance",
            "salary",
            "royalties"
        ],
        "answer": "royalties"
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "question": "He could not use the machine he bought effectively because the supplier did not include the ______ in the carton",
        "options": [
            "diary",
            "manual",
            "inventory",
            "record"
        ],
        "answer": "manual"
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "question": "He cleaned the pen but he did not clean the because he could not bear the ______ of the pigs",
        "options": [
            "stable, neighing",
            "pen, bleats",
            "sty, grunts",
            "Hutch, squeals"
        ],
        "answer": "sty, grunts"
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "question": "Screeches is to parrot what ______ is to turkey",
        "options": [
            "croacks",
            "gobbles",
            "twitters",
            "coos"
        ],
        "answer": "gobbles"
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "question": "Waddles is to duck what ______ is to elephant",
        "options": [
            "swoops",
            "jogs",
            "trots",
            "ambles"
        ],
        "answer": "ambles"
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "question": "Which of the following is wrongly paired with the group?",
        "options": [
            "an army of soldiers",
            "a bench of bishops",
            "a brood of chickens",
            "a bench of ladies"
        ],
        "answer": "a bench of ladies"
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "question": "The first language skill possessed by man is_",
        "options": [
            "speaking",
            "listening",
            "reading",
            "writing"
        ],
        "answer": "listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "question": "Two of the common contexts in which students make use of the listening skill are",
        "options": [
            "lectures and seminars",
            "lectures and summons",
            "debates and songs",
            "seminars and music"
        ],
        "answer": "lectures and seminars"
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "question": "Which of the following is a practical way of achieving effective listening?",
        "options": [
            "keep prejudice",
            "use of cue words and sense signals",
            "reading",
            "focusing on the source rather than the message"
        ],
        "answer": "use of cue words and sense signals"
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "question": "When you listen with a view to rendering help to the speaker, this kind of listening is described as",
        "options": [
            "mute listening",
            "critical listening",
            "sympathetic listening",
            "empathic listening"
        ],
        "answer": "empathic listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "question": "One of the following linguistic cues enables a listener to follow an oral text in listening",
        "options": [
            "Following sentence collectors",
            "following sentence patterns",
            "avoiding sequence of words",
            "speedy reading"
        ],
        "answer": "following sentence patterns"
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "question": "Two factors which contribute to poor listening are and",
        "options": [
            "emotional problems and motivated attention",
            "poor intellectual ability and impatience",
            "health factors and purposeful listening",
            "attitudinal problems and audience participating"
        ],
        "answer": "poor intellectual ability and impatience"
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "question": "______ are receptive skills",
        "options": [
            "listening and writing",
            "reading and speaking",
            "reading and listening",
            "speaking and listening"
        ],
        "answer": "reading and listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "question": "The use of gestures in communication may be described as",
        "options": [
            "facial expression",
            "verbal communication",
            "communication problem",
            "paralinguistic message"
        ],
        "answer": "paralinguistic message"
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "question": "Fatigue and lack of motivation are examples of ______ factors responsible for poor listening",
        "options": [
            "psychological",
            "physiological",
            "physical",
            "attitudinal"
        ],
        "answer": "psychological"
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "question": "The active process of receiving, constructing meaning from, and responding to spoken or non-verbal message can be called",
        "options": [
            "reading",
            "hearing",
            "listening",
            "interaction"
        ],
        "answer": "listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true?",
        "options": [
            "One has control over what one hears",
            "One has control over what one listening to",
            "One has no control over what one listening to",
            "Listening is a productive skill"
        ],
        "answer": "One has control over what one listening to"
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "question": "The process of making sense of a message is termed",
        "options": [
            "conceiving",
            "understanding",
            "attending",
            "responding"
        ],
        "answer": "understanding"
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "question": "The act of paying attention to a signal is",
        "options": [
            "listening",
            "attending",
            "responding",
            "socializing"
        ],
        "answer": "attending"
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "question": "One major function of examination is",
        "options": [
            "evaluation of students' performance",
            "instilling discipline in students",
            "accessing information",
            "formation of goals"
        ],
        "answer": "evaluation of students' performance"
    },
    {
        "id": 188,
        "question": "During lectures, a student makes use of_ skills more than others",
        "options": [
            "speaking and reading",
            "reading and writing",
            "listening and writing",
            "speaking and listening"
        ],
        "answer": "listening and writing"
    },
    {
        "id": 189,
        "question": "In order for one to acquire a language, ______ takes precedence",
        "options": [
            "speaking",
            "writing",
            "reading",
            "listening"
        ],
        "answer": "listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 190,
        "question": "______ ranks first among the language skills",
        "options": [
            "reading",
            "listening",
            "writing",
            "speaking"
        ],
        "answer": "listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "question": "The type of listening in which we search for new information is called",
        "options": [
            "passive listening",
            "transactional listening",
            "elliptical listening",
            "pseudo listening"
        ],
        "answer": "transactional listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "question": "The kind of listening you adopt when others seek help from you is called",
        "options": [
            "empathic listening",
            "emotional listening",
            "critical listening",
            "evaluative listening"
        ],
        "answer": "empathic listening"
    },
    {
        "id": 193,
        "question": "Thinking a deep thought about something else while listening to a message or lecture is an example of",
        "options": [
            "physiological noise",
            "passive attention",
            "environmental noise",
            "psychological noise"
        ],
        "answer": "psychological noise"
    },
    {
        "id": 194,
        "question": "The most important thing about listening is",
        "options": [
            "paying attention in order to receive information",
            "the abilities to receive information, process it, assimilate and retain it for future use",
            "the act of receiving sound waves",
            "being conscious and focusing on the speaker"
        ],
        "answer": "the abilities to receive information, process it, assimilate and retain it for future use"
    },
    {
        "id": 195,
        "question": "Two characteristics of listening are and",
        "options": [
            "learning and attending",
            "reviewing and revising",
            "thinking and reasoning",
            "searching and discovering"
        ],
        "answer": "learning and attending"
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "question": "When a listener listens with the purpose of recreating a situation after listening to it, it is called _listening",
        "options": [
            "purposeful",
            "creative",
            "secondary",
            "empathic"
        ],
        "answer": "creative"
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "question": "The listener's state can be sub-divided into _____, ____ and ____",
        "options": [
            "Emotional, sensory and physical",
            "occasion, psychological and attentional",
            "intellectual, physiological and psychological",
            "exterior, interior and intrinsic"
        ],
        "answer": "intellectual, physiological and psychological"
    },
    {
        "id": 198,
        "question": "Which of the following qualities in the speaker inhibit listening efficiency?",
        "options": [
            "nasal tone",
            "education level",
            "purpose",
            "knowledge of the subject matter"
        ],
        "answer": "nasal tone"
    },
    {
        "id": 199,
        "question": "The status, power, and authority of a speaker directly effect the way his audience listens to him",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "none of the above",
            "all of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "id": 200,
        "question": "The availability of space, ventilation, tidiness, and orderliness of space refer to",
        "options": [
            "organization",
            "environment",
            "accommodation",
            "setting arrangement"
        ],
        "answer": "setting arrangement"
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "question": "In order to improve and promote effective listening, one of the following is important",
        "options": [
            "Focus your attention on the message",
            "avoid eliciting meaning from the speech",
            "there should be no relationship between one's background knowledge and what one listens to",
            "avoid note-taking because causes loss of memory"
        ],
        "answer": "Focus your attention on the message"
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "question": "A situation where a listener receives too much information than is necessary is called",
        "options": [
            "rapid thought",
            "message splash",
            "message overload",
            "message quake"
        ],
        "answer": "message overload"
    },
    {
        "id": 203,
        "question": "The intellectual state of the listener includes ____ and ____",
        "options": [
            "age and readiness",
            "physical fitness and fitness exercises",
            "motivation and delivery",
            "intent and mindset"
        ],
        "answer": "age and readiness"
    },
    {
        "id": 204,
        "question": "The opposite of legitimate is",
        "options": [
            "illegitimate",
            "illegitimate",
            "dislegitimate",
            "ambiguous"
        ],
        "answer": "illegitimate"
    },
    {
        "id": 205,
        "question": "Which of the following words is spelt correctly?",
        "options": [
            "questionnaire",
            "questionnaire",
            "questionear",
            "questional"
        ],
        "answer": "questionnaire"
    },
    {
        "id": 206,
        "question": "Thinning, gestation and grafting belong to ______ discipline",
        "options": [
            "religion",
            "agriculture",
            "zoology",
            "craftsmanship"
        ],
        "answer": "agriculture"
    },
    {
        "id": 207,
        "question": "Pick out the odd word from the list",
        "options": [
            "ballot",
            "autopsy",
            "wound",
            "cava"
        ],
        "answer": "ballot"
    },
    {
        "id": 208,
        "question": "The most important feature of reading is ______",
        "options": [
            "scanning",
            "skimming",
            "comprehension",
            "drilling"
        ],
        "answer": "comprehension"
    },
    {
        "id": 209,
        "question": "Comprehension takes place at ______ levels of meaning",
        "options": [
            "four",
            "five",
            "three",
            "two"
        ],
        "answer": "three"
    },
    {
        "id": 210,
        "question": "The skill which a reader needs in order to understand a text is skill",
        "options": [
            "work attack",
            "text attack",
            "mind attack",
            "meaning attack"
        ],
        "answer": "text attack"
    },
    {
        "id": 211,
        "question": "The glossary of a book can help a reader to find information about",
        "options": [
            "familiar words in the text",
            "antonyms",
            "pseudonyms",
            "strange words in a text"
        ],
        "answer": "strange words in a text"
    },
    {
        "id": 212,
        "question": "Another name for the conjectural level of comprehensive is",
        "options": [
            "associative",
            "assimilative",
            "inferential",
            "literal"
        ],
        "answer": "inferential"
    },
    {
        "id": 213,
        "question": "______ is useful for the determination of the functional values of sentences",
        "options": [
            "discourse makers",
            "sentence markers",
            "sentence patterns",
            "sentence structures"
        ],
        "answer": "sentence patterns"
    },
    {
        "id": 214,
        "question": "One example of word attack skills is",
        "options": [
            "the use of dictionary",
            "the use of vocabulary",
            "the use of information",
            "the use of phonics"
        ],
        "answer": "the use of phonics"
    },
    {
        "id": 215,
        "question": "______ is moving forward and backward during reading",
        "options": [
            "obsession",
            "regress",
            "recession",
            "appreciation"
        ],
        "answer": "regress"
    },
    {
        "id": 216,
        "question": "Glancing through a text rapidly for a specific piece of information is called",
        "options": [
            "scanning",
            "skimming",
            "extensive reading",
            "intensive reading"
        ],
        "answer": "scanning"
    },
    {
        "id": 217,
        "question": "______ involves reading of large quantities of material",
        "options": [
            "silent reading",
            "extensive reading",
            "intensive reading",
            "scanning"
        ],
        "answer": "extensive reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 218,
        "question": "The practice of whispering words or moving one's lips while reading is called",
        "options": [
            "regression",
            "vocalization",
            "oral reading",
            "vocal reading"
        ],
        "answer": "vocalization"
    },
    {
        "id": 219,
        "question": "The last 'R' in SQ3R stands for",
        "options": [
            "review",
            "recall",
            "read",
            "remind"
        ],
        "answer": "review"
    },
    {
        "id": 220,
        "question": "Preview involves locating one of the following",
        "options": [
            "the date of publication",
            "topic sentence",
            "argument structure",
            "documentation style"
        ],
        "answer": "the date of publication"
    },
    {
        "id": 221,
        "question": "Intensive and extensive reading may be described as",
        "options": [
            "oral reading",
            "silent reading",
            "public speeches",
            "announcements"
        ],
        "answer": "silent reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 222,
        "question": "Oral reading involves a tripartite communication mode and they are ______, ______ and ______",
        "options": [
            "the text, the reader and the audience",
            "the author, the reader and the text",
            "the reader, the audience and the scene",
            "situation, the audience and the writer"
        ],
        "answer": "the text, the reader and the audience"
    },
    {
        "id": 223,
        "question": "The work of studying facts again in order to learn them is called",
        "options": [
            "examination",
            "revising",
            "ruminating",
            "brainstorming"
        ],
        "answer": "revising"
    },
    {
        "id": 224,
        "question": "One advantage of having a reading group is",
        "options": [
            "it creates familiarization among the members",
            "it help to maintain friendship",
            "difficult questions are resolved by the group",
            "the readers evaluate their teacher in the process"
        ],
        "answer": "difficult questions are resolved by the group"
    },
    {
        "id": 225,
        "question": "The first level of reading comprehension is the",
        "options": [
            "factual",
            "critical",
            "inferential",
            "evaluation"
        ],
        "answer": "factual"
    },
    {
        "id": 226,
        "question": "Finger pointing and regress impede",
        "options": [
            "understanding",
            "reading",
            "listening",
            "speaking"
        ],
        "answer": "reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 227,
        "question": "_____, _____ and ____ are the approaches to reading",
        "options": [
            "Skimming, scanning, and intensive reading",
            "Scanning, intensive reading and vocalization",
            "Skimming, scanning and regression",
            "Intensive reading, extensive reading and fast reading"
        ],
        "answer": "Skimming, scanning, and intensive reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 228,
        "question": "At the inferential level of comprehension, the emphasis is usually on the _____ meaning",
        "options": [
            "explicit",
            "implicit",
            "impending",
            "ordinary"
        ],
        "answer": "implicit"
    },
    {
        "id": 229,
        "question": "In the taxonomy of language skills, _____ rank last",
        "options": [
            "speaking",
            "reading",
            "listening",
            "writing"
        ],
        "answer": "writing"
    },
    {
        "id": 230,
        "question": "____ involves a deliberate and conscious effort to increase by learning the stock of knowledge a person has",
        "options": [
            "study",
            "learning",
            "skill",
            "reading"
        ],
        "answer": "study"
    },
    {
        "id": 231,
        "question": "ranks third among the language skills",
        "options": [
            "listening",
            "speaking",
            "writing",
            "reading"
        ],
        "answer": "reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 232,
        "question": "____ enables a reader to remember what he has read or learnt",
        "options": [
            "mnemonics",
            "topic sentence",
            "revision",
            "examination"
        ],
        "answer": "mnemonics"
    },
    {
        "id": 233,
        "question": "Two forms of mnemonics are ____ and ____",
        "options": [
            "synonyms and antonyms",
            "acronyms and acrostics",
            "critical and appreciative",
            "major and minor"
        ],
        "answer": "acronyms and acrostics"
    },
    {
        "id": 234,
        "question": "An interaction between a text and the reader in which information is passed from the writer to the reader is called",
        "options": [
            "assimilation",
            "processing",
            "reception",
            "reading"
        ],
        "answer": "reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 235,
        "question": "Reading according to Bloom's taxonomy include ____ and ____",
        "options": [
            "faster and critical",
            "oral and silent",
            "scanning and skimming",
            "inferential and analytical"
        ],
        "answer": "oral and silent"
    },
    {
        "id": 236,
        "question": "When one reads with a specific focus on grammatical forms, discourse markers etc, it is referred to as",
        "options": [
            "intensive reading",
            "extensive reading",
            "oral reading",
            "silent reading"
        ],
        "answer": "intensive reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 237,
        "question": "In extensive reading, the reader usually",
        "options": [
            "selects few materials to be read",
            "focuses on discourse markers",
            "reads a large quantities materials",
            "reads with a view to passing an examination"
        ],
        "answer": "reads a large quantities materials"
    },
    {
        "id": 238,
        "question": "Skimming is an aspect of ____ reading",
        "options": [
            "oral",
            "silent",
            "total",
            "critical"
        ],
        "answer": "silent"
    },
    {
        "id": 239,
        "question": "enhances faster and extensive reading",
        "options": [
            "scanning",
            "skimming",
            "evaluation",
            "vocalization"
        ],
        "answer": "skimming"
    },
    {
        "id": 240,
        "question": "When a reader is interested in locating a particular piece of information in a text, the reading technique is called",
        "options": [
            "mnemonics",
            "scanning",
            "preview",
            "skimming"
        ],
        "answer": "scanning"
    },
    {
        "id": 241,
        "question": "The level of reading in which the reader critiques the text and incorporates his thoughts is referred to as",
        "options": [
            "analytical",
            "preview",
            "discovery",
            "collocation"
        ],
        "answer": "analytical"
    },
    {
        "id": 242,
        "question": "Another name for evaluative level of reading is_",
        "options": [
            "inferential",
            "synthetical",
            "literal",
            "analytical"
        ],
        "answer": "analytical"
    },
    {
        "id": 243,
        "question": "The full meaning of SQ3R is",
        "options": [
            "scanning, question, revision and re-reading",
            "survey, question, reason and revision",
            "survey, question, read and re-read",
            "scrutiny, quick, reason and rate"
        ],
        "answer": "survey, question, read and re-read"
    },
    {
        "id": 244,
        "question": "The problem which affects speed and accuracy of printed word recognition is called",
        "options": [
            "orthographic processing deficit",
            "comprehension deficit",
            "double deficit",
            "phonological deficit"
        ],
        "answer": "orthographic processing deficit"
    },
    {
        "id": 245,
        "question": "A reader who has a prominent and specific problem in either phonological or rapid print is said to have a in word recognition",
        "options": [
            "complex deficit",
            "single deficit",
            "double deficit",
            "major deficit"
        ],
        "answer": "single deficit"
    },
    {
        "id": 246,
        "question": "The effects of linguistic problem encountered in reading include_____, and_____",
        "options": [
            "phonological, orthographic and semantic",
            "morphological, structural and comprehension",
            "intonation, stress and wordings",
            "phonological, morphological and sentential"
        ],
        "answer": "phonological, orthographic and semantic"
    },
    {
        "id": 247,
        "question": "is peculiar to children with sociolinguistic disabilities, vocabulary weakness and learning difficulties that affect abstract reasoning and logical thinking",
        "options": [
            "phonological deficit",
            "morphological deficit",
            "comprehension deficit",
            "processing, speed deficit"
        ],
        "answer": "comprehension deficit"
    },
    {
        "id": 248,
        "question": "___ is the reading disability characterized by difficulties with accurate word recognition, decoding and spelling",
        "options": [
            "insomnia",
            "dyslexia",
            "deformity",
            "impairment"
        ],
        "answer": "dyslexia"
    },
    {
        "id": 249,
        "question": "Emotional and psychological problems can be solved by",
        "options": [
            "setting new reading goals and targets",
            "reading very fast",
            "practicing different kinds of texts",
            "jotting and note-taking"
        ],
        "answer": "setting new reading goals and targets"
    },
    {
        "id": 250,
        "question": "Pointing to words and single word reading usually go with",
        "options": [
            "environmental problem",
            "visualization",
            "regression",
            "vocalization"
        ],
        "answer": "vocalization"
    },
    {
        "id": 251,
        "question": "Techniques of faster reading are _____, ____ and ____",
        "options": [
            "intensive, extensive and oral reading",
            "skimming, scanning and SQ3R",
            "critical, evaluation and literal reading",
            "survey, visualization and contextualization"
        ],
        "answer": "skimming, scanning and SQ3R"
    },
    {
        "id": 252,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true?",
        "options": [
            "reading with questions is a good study technique",
            "reading with a purpose wastes more time",
            "reading is important only during examinations",
            "reading excludes note-taking"
        ],
        "answer": "reading with questions is a good study technique"
    },
    {
        "id": 253,
        "question": "The meaning carrying sentence in every paragraph is called",
        "options": [
            "introductory sentence",
            "connotative sentence",
            "topic sentence",
            "literal sentence"
        ],
        "answer": "topic sentence"
    },
    {
        "id": 254,
        "question": "______ technique of reading advocates that a reader should not read any material with a pre-conceived notion",
        "options": [
            "reading with a purpose",
            "reading with questions",
            "sense links",
            "flexibility"
        ],
        "answer": "flexibility"
    },
    {
        "id": 255,
        "question": "Which of the following statements is not ?",
        "options": [
            "memorization is an efficient learning technique",
            "pre-taking involves writing down only the important words",
            "preview is encourages faster reading",
            "italicized words help o draw the reader's attention"
        ],
        "answer": "memorization is an efficient learning technique"
    },
    {
        "id": 256,
        "question": "One feature of intensive reading is that",
        "options": [
            "it is usually classroom based",
            "students read as much as possible",
            "reading speed is usually faster",
            "students look for different words only"
        ],
        "answer": "it is usually classroom based"
    },
    {
        "id": 257,
        "question": "One of the materials to be read under oral reading is_",
        "options": [
            "novels",
            "journals",
            "books",
            "public speeches"
        ],
        "answer": "public speeches"
    },
    {
        "id": 258,
        "question": "A list of book, articles and other publications used for research is called",
        "options": [
            "glossary",
            "bibliography",
            "documentation",
            "appendix"
        ],
        "answer": "bibliography"
    },
    {
        "id": 259,
        "question": "The apendix, glossary, listed abbreviation and bibliography are found in the part of research paper",
        "options": [
            "preliminary pages",
            "subsidiary pages",
            "front pages",
            "footnotes"
        ],
        "answer": "subsidiary pages"
    },
    {
        "id": 260,
        "question": "Ibid is used in documentation to-avoid",
        "options": [
            "repetition",
            "plagiarism",
            "bibliography",
            "long essay"
        ],
        "answer": "repetition"
    },
    {
        "id": 261,
        "question": "Ibid means",
        "options": [
            "as omitted above",
            "as cited below",
            "as cited above",
            "as recommended above"
        ],
        "answer": "as cited above"
    },
    {
        "id": 262,
        "question": "ISBN in a book means",
        "options": [
            "interested second book number",
            "international series book number",
            "international standard book number",
            "internet statement book name"
        ],
        "answer": "international standard book number"
    },
    {
        "id": 263,
        "question": "When a table of contents gives details of the contents, it is said to be",
        "options": [
            "comprehensive",
            "analytical",
            "non-analytical",
            "serial"
        ],
        "answer": "analytical"
    },
    {
        "id": 264,
        "question": "The blurb of a book contains information about the ______ and the ______",
        "options": [
            "title and content",
            "book and author",
            "reference and endnotes",
            "reader and lesson"
        ],
        "answer": "title and content"
    },
    {
        "id": 265,
        "question": "et al means",
        "options": [
            "all others",
            "and others",
            "some others",
            "few others"
        ],
        "answer": "and others"
    },
    {
        "id": 266,
        "question": "The major criticism against the classic style of documentation is its heavy dependence on ______ terms in making cross reference",
        "options": [
            "Greek",
            "American",
            "British",
            "Latin"
        ],
        "answer": "Latin"
    },
    {
        "id": 267,
        "question": "___ and ___ can be found in the subsidiary pages of a paper",
        "options": [
            "bibliography and glossary",
            "glossary and preface",
            "acknowledgements and dedication",
            "institutional name and date"
        ],
        "answer": "bibliography and glossary"
    },
    {
        "id": 268,
        "question": "The first step to be taken in term paper writing is__",
        "options": [
            "gathering materials",
            "assessing the materials",
            "choosing a topic",
            "writing he report"
        ],
        "answer": "choosing a topic"
    },
    {
        "id": 269,
        "question": "In selecting a topic for a term paper, one should bear two of the following in mind",
        "options": [
            "Familiarity with the topic and interest in the topic",
            "The format and documentation style",
            "Suitability of the topic and footnote",
            "Library source and internet source"
        ],
        "answer": "Familiarity with the topic and interest in the topic"
    },
    {
        "id": 270,
        "question": "MLA stands for",
        "options": [
            "modern learners association",
            "modern language acquisition",
            "modern language association",
            "modern league association"
        ],
        "answer": "modern language association"
    },
    {
        "id": 271,
        "question": "Two importance of documentation are ___ and ___",
        "options": [
            "to avoid charges against plagiarism and provide sources for further reading",
            "to conceal sources and avoid verification",
            "provide sources for verification and prohibit further reading",
            "acknowledge sources and suffer plagiarism"
        ],
        "answer": "to avoid charges against plagiarism and provide sources for further reading"
    },
    {
        "id": 272,
        "question": "___ style of documentation is commonly used in the sciences",
        "options": [
            "MLA",
            "APA",
            "AMA",
            "PAA"
        ],
        "answer": "APA"
    },
    {
        "id": 273,
        "question": "False assumption of authorship is described as",
        "options": [
            "freedom",
            "plagiarism",
            "authorization",
            "impersonation"
        ],
        "answer": "plagiarism"
    },
    {
        "id": 274,
        "question": "The preliminary page of a research contain two of the following",
        "options": [
            "table of contents and reference",
            "bibliography and dedication",
            "preface and dedication",
            "glossary and appendix"
        ],
        "answer": "preface and dedication"
    },
    {
        "id": 275,
        "question": "The part of the research work which shows the list of chapter headings, sub-heading and pages and where they are found is",
        "options": [
            "the table of contents",
            "references",
            "bibliography",
            "works cited"
        ],
        "answer": "the table of contents"
    },
    {
        "id": 276,
        "question": "Works cited is to MLA what ____ is to APA",
        "options": [
            "bibliography",
            "index",
            "appendix",
            "references"
        ],
        "answer": "references"
    },
    {
        "id": 277,
        "question": "The cover page of a term paper is designed to contain one of the following",
        "options": [
            "the preface",
            "the name of the institution",
            "the importance of term paper",
            "the acknowledgement"
        ],
        "answer": "the name of the institution"
    },
    {
        "id": 278,
        "question": "___part of the research paper contains the list of the names of persons who contributed to success of the research",
        "options": [
            "the preface",
            "the dedication",
            "the acknowledgements",
            "the main text"
        ],
        "answer": "the acknowledgements"
    },
    {
        "id": 279,
        "question": "Brainstorming means",
        "options": [
            "trying to develop ideas and thinking of ways of solving a problem",
            "assessing the implications of a research",
            "collecting data",
            "analyzing data"
        ],
        "answer": "trying to develop ideas and thinking of ways of solving a problem"
    },
    {
        "id": 280,
        "question": "What is likely to follow after brainstorming is_",
        "options": [
            "the damage of brain cells",
            "re-writing stage",
            "fast breathing",
            "cooling of the brain"
        ],
        "answer": "re-writing stage"
    },
    {
        "id": 281,
        "question": "Revising stage takes care of",
        "options": [
            "wrong spellings and expressions",
            "documentation and referencing",
            "formatting and publishing",
            "recommendation and conclusion"
        ],
        "answer": "wrong spellings and expressions"
    },
    {
        "id": 282,
        "question": "The stage where a researcher handles the main work of the report writing is the",
        "options": [
            "brainstorming",
            "pre-writing",
            "writing",
            "revising"
        ],
        "answer": "writing"
    },
    {
        "id": 283,
        "question": "The ___part of a research work contains information on how the work is organized chapter by chapter, how data was collected and the challenges encountered in the process",
        "options": [
            "dedication",
            "acknowledgements",
            "the table of contents",
            "the preface"
        ],
        "answer": "the preface"
    },
    {
        "id": 284,
        "question": "Two forms of documentation are___and___",
        "options": [
            "bibliographical and textual",
            "scientific and non-scientific",
            "American and British",
            "long and short"
        ],
        "answer": "bibliographical and textual"
    },
    {
        "id": 285,
        "question": "______ shows the extent of the writer's citations",
        "options": [
            "reference",
            "documentation",
            "dedication",
            "preface"
        ],
        "answer": "documentation"
    },
    {
        "id": 286,
        "question": "Textual documentation contains_",
        "options": [
            "additional facts, contents and relevant explanations",
            "major points, index and preface",
            "glossary, sub-headings and conclusion",
            "authors, institutions and resources"
        ],
        "answer": "additional facts, contents and relevant explanations"
    },
    {
        "id": 287,
        "question": "APA means",
        "options": [
            "African Peoples Alliance",
            "authority Paper Assembled",
            "American Psychological Association",
            "American Peoples Apprentice"
        ],
        "answer": "American Psychological Association"
    },
    {
        "id": 288,
        "question": "The MLA is commonly used in the",
        "options": [
            "biological sciences",
            "physical sciences",
            "humanities",
            "natural sciences"
        ],
        "answer": "humanities"
    },
    {
        "id": 289,
        "question": "______ aids cross-referencing of materials",
        "options": [
            "APA",
            "MLA",
            "documentation",
            "quotations"
        ],
        "answer": "documentation"
    },
    {
        "id": 290,
        "question": "______ is the method scholars use to acknowledge sources of information consulted during research",
        "options": [
            "acknowledgements",
            "quotations",
            "documentation",
            "abstracts"
        ],
        "answer": "documentation"
    },
    {
        "id": 291,
        "question": "The two basic forms of citation style are ______ and ______ styles",
        "options": [
            "classic and triple entry",
            "single and double entry",
            "formal and informal",
            "British and American"
        ],
        "answer": "classic and triple entry"
    },
    {
        "id": 292,
        "question": "The citation \"Ugwu (2016:33) observes\" represents form of citation",
        "options": [
            "classic",
            "triple",
            "double",
            "British"
        ],
        "answer": "double"
    },
    {
        "id": 293,
        "question": "___ is an acknowledgement a writer makes when quoting directly or paraphrasing another writer's work",
        "options": [
            "the reference",
            "the quotation",
            "the endnotes",
            "the index"
        ],
        "answer": "the quotation"
    },
    {
        "id": 294,
        "question": "Three types of documentation are____,____and____",
        "options": [
            "references, quotations and citations",
            "references, bibliography and endnotes",
            "classic, triple and double",
            "American, British and Latin"
        ],
        "answer": "references, quotations and citations"
    },
    {
        "id": 295,
        "question": "___ indicates the omission of a word or a passage with three periods",
        "options": [
            "glossary",
            "endnote",
            "footnote",
            "Ellipsis"
        ],
        "answer": "Ellipsis"
    },
    {
        "id": 296,
        "question": "A simple statement of opinion which an entire research work is designed to support is called__",
        "options": [
            "abstract",
            "thesis",
            "data",
            "superscript"
        ],
        "answer": "thesis"
    },
    {
        "id": 297,
        "question": "The last information on the cover page of a term paper is the",
        "options": [
            "name of the writer",
            "name of institution",
            "registration number of student",
            "date of publication"
        ],
        "answer": "date of publication"
    },
    {
        "id": 298,
        "question": "The activity of individual information about something that you are interested in or need to know more about is called",
        "options": [
            "thesis",
            "research",
            "project",
            "analysis"
        ],
        "answer": "research"
    },
    {
        "id": 299,
        "question": "___describes how speech sounds are produced",
        "options": [
            "Auditory Phonetics",
            "Articulator Phonetics",
            "Stress",
            "Intonation"
        ],
        "answer": "Articulator Phonetics"
    },
    {
        "id": 300,
        "question": "The human speech production begins from the",
        "options": [
            "Mouth",
            "Lungs",
            "Glottis",
            "Larynx"
        ],
        "answer": "Lungs"
    }
];